Thomas Hart Photographs MS093
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Thomas Hart Photographs
1966 -- 1983
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Hart, Thomas M.
MS093
248 Digital Object(s)
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Biographical / Historical
Thomas M. Hart, born June 14, 1946, graduated from Tufts with a B.S. in Biology in 1968. He took the photographs in this collection both while he was a student and after his graduation.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains photographs taken by Tufts student Tom Hart.
University history; Photographs; Alumni collections
- Photographs, 1966 -- 1983; MS093.001; 248 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains photographs by Tufts student Tom Hart. Includes snapshots of student gatherings and events.
  Arrangement
  This series is not arranged.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Intramural football match, 1967; MS093.001.DO.01737; Hart, Tom
    People and events may not be correctly identified.
    People; Football
  - David Farrell, Sandy Farrell and two unidentified people at homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.01934; Hart, Tom
    People; Events; Farrell, David
  - Dr. Chester Roys, Lecturer in Biology Department, in his laboratory in Dana Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04705; Hart, Tom
    People; Professors; Roys, Chester
  - Dr. Norton H. Nickerson at microscope, Frank Zungolo on his left, botany lab, Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04706; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Laboratories; Nickerson, Norton H.; Zungolo, Frank
  - Dr. Chester Roys, Lecturer in Biology Department, in his laboratory in Dana Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04707; Hart, Tom
  - Dr. Chester Roys in Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04708; Hart, Tom
  - Dr. Norton H. Nickerson at microscope, Frank Zungolo on his left, botany lab, Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04709; Hart, Tom
  - West Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04710; Hart, Tom
    Buildings
  - West Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04711; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown people, Pearson Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04712; Hart, Tom
    People; Laboratories
  - Unknown person, Pearson Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04713; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown person, Pearson Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04714; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown person, Pearson Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04715; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown person, Pearson Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04716; Hart, Tom
  - Dr. Mumford, Astronomy Department, in Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04717; Hart, Tom
    People; Professors; Mumford, Dr.
  - Dr. Mumford, Astronomy Department, in Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04718; Hart, Tom
  - Dr. Mumford, Astronomy Department, in Barnum Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04719; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown person, Michael Laboratory, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04720; Hart, Tom
  - Unknown person, Michael Laboratory, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04721; Hart, Tom
  - Stuffed head, Michael Laboratory, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04722; Hart, Tom
    Laboratories
  - Hillside House intramural football team, front row: Joe Pedulla, "Pudge," Bob Simpson, "Mojo Man," Wayne Prescott. Rear: John Mahony, John Capone, Dave Bramley, Ron DiPerna, Vin Gasbarro, 1968; MS093.001.DO.04723; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Football; Pedulla, Joe; "Pudge"; Simpson, Bob; "Mojo Man"; Prescott, Wayne; Mahoney, John; Capone, John; Bramley, David; DiPerna, Ron; Gasbarro, Vin
  - Dorm room in Wren Hall, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04724; Hart, Tom
    Dormitories; Interior views
  - Dorm room in Wren Hall, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04725; Hart, Tom
  - Dorm room in Wren Hall, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04726; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House football, front: Peter Wadler, John Minichiello, unkown, and Don Trites. Rear: #6 is Mark Malone, 1967; MS093.001.DO.04727; Hart, Tom
    Students; Football; People; Wadler, Peter; Minichiello, John; Trites, Don; Malone, Mark
  - Unkown student playing tennis, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04728; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Tennis
  - Hillside House football team, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04729; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Football
  - Hillside House intramural football team, front row: Joe Pedulla, "Pudge," Bob Simpson, "Mojo Man," Wayne Prescott. Rear: John Mahony, John Capone, Dave Bramley, Ron DiPerna, Vin Gasbarro, 1968; MS093.001.DO.04730; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04731; Hart, Tom
    Football; Students; People
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04732; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football team, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04733; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04734; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04735; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04736; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04738; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04739; Hart, Tom
  - Intramural football at Fletcher Field, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04740; Hart, Tom
  - Wayne Prescott diving for football, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04741; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Football; Prescott, Wayne
  - Dave Bramley makes a catch during a football game, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04742; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Football; Bramley, David
  - Dave Bramley cathing a football, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04743; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House on offense during a football game, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04744; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Football
  - Hillside House huddle, football game, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04745; Hart, Tom
  - Ellis Oval, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04747; Hart, Tom
  - Ellis Oval, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04748; Hart, Tom
  - Stairs behind Bendetson and Packard Halls, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04749; Hart, Tom
    Stairs; Buildings; Exterior views
  - Intramural tennis after a rainstorm, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04750; Hart, Tom
    Tennis; People; Students
  - Wessell Library, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04751; Hart, Tom
    Libraries; Exterior views
  - Wessell Library, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04752; Hart, Tom
  - Front stairs of Eaton Hall, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04753; Hart, Tom
  - Looking downhill at Lincoln Filene Center, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04754; Hart, Tom
    Buildings; Exterior views
  - Lawn in front of Wessell Library, towards College Ave., 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04755; Hart, Tom
    Librarians; Exterior views
  - Hillside House residents launching a weather balloon, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04756; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Meteorological balloons
  - Hillside House residents launching a weather balloon, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04757; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents launching a weather balloon, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04758; Hart, Tom
    Image is "positive," not "negative." Designed for balck and white slides.
  - Carmichael Hall from the top of Wren Hall, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04759; Hart, Tom
  - Anti-war poster on Wessell Library wall, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04760; Hart, Tom
    Poster
  - Two students in front of Goddard Chapel, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04761; Hart, Tom
    Students; People
  - Stairs to Wessell Library, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04762; Hart, Tom
    Libraries; Exterior views; People
  - Students on the roof of Wessell Library, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04763; Hart, Tom
    Students; Libraries
  - Poster of Bridgette Bardot (?) in dorm room, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04764; Hart, Tom
    Poster; Dormitories
  - Barnum Hall and Dana Laboratory, March, 1969; MS093.001.DO.04765; Hart, Tom
  - Stairs from Barnum Hall to Professors Row, 1970; MS093.001.DO.04766; Hart, Tom
    People; Stairs
  - John Marrs, A1967, on stairs leading from Barnum Hall, 1970; MS093.001.DO.04767; Hart, Tom
    People; Marrs, John
  - Barnum Hall looking towards Professors Row, 1970; MS093.001.DO.04768; Hart, Tom
    Trees; Lawns
  - Gate around campus, 1970; MS093.001.DO.04769; Hart, Tom
    Gates
  - Lawn around College Ave., 1970; MS093.001.DO.04770; Hart, Tom
    Lawns
  - View of Wessell Library at night, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04771; Hart, Tom
  - Home of Steven Costa, E1968, Somerville, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04772; Hart, Tom
    Houses; Costa, Steven
  - Wren Hall, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04773; Hart, Tom
    Dormitories; Exterior views
  - View from Ballou Hall to Bendetson and Packard Halls, 1966 -- 1967; MS093.001.DO.04774; Hart, Tom
    Lawns; Buildings; Exterior views
  - Jumbo photographers, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04775; Unknown
    Front row: all unknown, except Kawrence J. Kunz, A1967 (third from right); second row: unkown, John Michiello, E1969, Hraire Kurkjian, E1968, unknown, Albert Comeau, E1966, Thomas Hart, A1968, David Breen, Ron DiPerna, A1968, John Mahoney, E1969; third row: Anthony Cortese, E1968, Jospeh Pedulla, E1969, David Bramley, E1969, David Gold, A1969, Neil Olansky, E1969, James Stewart, E1969, 1966.
    Student activities; Students; Portraits, Group; Hart, Thomas; Jumbo Book
  - Campaign photo from Haille "Hi You" Selassie, directing traffic on College Ave., 1967; MS093.001.DO.04776; Hart, Tom
    Mayoralty
  - Members of W1KN in basement of West Hall, 1901 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04777; Unknown
    Identified as: Dick Holland, Steve Gilbert, Larry Koolkin, and Thomas Hart.
    Students; Radio Stations; Student activities; Hart, Thomas
  - Before 'sled dog' race on Professors Row, 1968; MS093.001.DO.04778; Unknown
    Tom Hart running in center of image.
    Students; Events; Hart, Thomas
  - Mark Malone, Gordon Dobey, and Joe Martin bringing balloons to Kids Day in Alumnae Hall gym, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04779; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Malone, Mark; Dobey, Gordon; Martin, Joseph
  - Students in Michael Chem Lab, Peter Wadler in front of door, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04780; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Laboratories; Wadler, Peter
  - Joe Martin in Michael Chemistry Laboratory, 1967 -- 1968; MS093.001.DO.04781; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Laboratories; Martin, Joseph
  - Graduation, Joe DiSimone in center, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04782; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Commencement; DiSimone, Joseph
  - Graduation, head of procession, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04783; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Commencement
  - Dr. Balmuth, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04784; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement; Balmuth, Dr.
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04785; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement
  - Graduation procession towards Carmichael Hall, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04786; Hart, Tom
  - George Daley, center, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04787; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement; Daley, George
  - Bendetson Hall, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04788; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04789; Hart, Tom
    People; Commencement
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04790; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04791; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04792; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04793; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04794; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04795; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04796; Hart, Tom
  - Conferring of degrees, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04797; Hart, Tom
  - George Daley, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04798; Hart, Tom
    People; Commencement; Daley, George
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04799; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, unknown person, Russ Collins, unknown person, George Daley, Bob Lee, Joe DiSimone, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04800; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement; Collins, Russ; Daley, George; Lee, Robert
  - Graduation, unknown person, Russ Collins, unknown person, George Daley, Bob Lee, Joe DiSimone, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04801; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, Joe DiSimone on right, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04802; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement; DiSimone, Joseph
  - Excitement at Ballou Hall, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04803; Hart, Tom
  - Start of graduation procession, Ballou Hall, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04804; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, Russ Collins (center) and Bob Lee, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04805; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Commencement; Collins, Russ; Lee, Robert
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04806; Hart, Tom
  - Policemen at graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04807; Hart, Tom
    People; Policemen; Commencement
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04808; Hart, Tom
  - New graduates: Rich Squillicioti, Joe DiSimone, Russ Collins, George Daley, and two unknown people, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04809; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Commencement; Squillicioti, Richard; DiSimone, Joseph; Collins, Russ; Daley, George
  - Pre-procession line up, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04810; Hart, Tom
  - Musicians tuning up, graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04811; Hart, Tom
    Music and musical performances; People; Students; Commencement
  - Graduation, Ballou Hall, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04812; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, view from Ballou Hall, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04813; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation stage, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04814; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04815; Hart, Tom
  - Graduation, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04816; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04817; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Softball
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04818; Hart, Tom
  - George Daley playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04819; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Softball; Daley, George
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04820; Hart, Tom
    People; Softball
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04821; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04822; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04823; Hart, Tom
  - Summer program at Tufts, looking at Talbot Ave., 1978; MS093.001.DO.04824; Hart, Tom
    People; Women
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04825; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04826; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04827; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04892; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04893; Hart, Tom
  - Softball rain delay, Russell Collins, John Kiley, and Ron Squillicioti, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04894; Hart, Tom
    People; Softball; Collins, Russ; Kiley, John; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Hillside House residents playing softball, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04895; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside residents playing softball, holding at first, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04896; Hart, Tom
  - Ron Squillicioti on sidelines, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04897; Hart, Tom
    People; Softball; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Softball game on diamond at Powderhouse Square, 1978; MS093.001.DO.04898; Hart, Tom
  - Spring concert at Wessell Library, May, 1971; MS093.001.DO.04899; Hart, Tom
    People; Concerts; Libraries
  - Spring concert at Wessell Library, May, 1971; MS093.001.DO.04900; Hart, Tom
  - Dr. Norton H. Nickerson eating lunch, ecology field trip, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04901; Hart, Tom
    People; Nickerson, Norton H.
  - Salt marsh ecosystem, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04902; Hart, Tom
    Salt marsh ecology
  - Salt marsh ecosystem, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04903; Hart, Tom
  - Studying beach ecology, Crane's beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04904; Hart, Tom
    Beaches
  - Sand dune ecosystem, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04905; Hart, Tom
    Sand dunes
  - Tom Hart driving through back country, Massachusetts, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04906; Hart, Tom
    Automobiles; People
  - Class photo, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04907; Hart, Tom
    People; Beaches
  - Student with binoculars, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04908; Hart, Tom
    People
  - Student and Dr. Nickerson searching for saltmarsh varmits, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04909; Hart, Tom
    People; Salt marsh ecology; Nickerson, Norton H.
  - Dune ecosystem, Crane's Beach, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04910; Hart, Tom
    Sand dunes; Beaches
  - Student and Dr. Nickerson searching for saltmarsh varmits, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04911; Hart, Tom
    Salt marsh ecology; People; Nickerson, Norton H.
  - Class on breakwater, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04912; Hart, Tom
  - Dune system, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04913; Hart, Tom
  - Sleuthing in salt marsh, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04914; Hart, Tom
    People; Salt marsh ecology
  - Sand dunes to water, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04915; Hart, Tom
  - Forest on Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04916; Hart, Tom
    People; Forests
  - Sand dunes, Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04918; Hart, Tom
    Sand dunes; People
  - Scene at Cape Cod, spring, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04919; Hart, Tom
    Beaches; People
  - John Hagopian performing a concert at Hillside House, E1970, G1972, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04920; Hart, Tom
    People; Music and musical performances; Hagopian, John
  - Band performance at Hillside House, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04921; Hart, Tom
  - Band performance at Hillside House, 1974; MS093.001.DO.04922; Hart, Tom
  - Ron Squillicioti, Homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04923; Hart, Tom
    People; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Dave Bramley, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04924; Hart, Tom
    People; Bramley, David
  - Bob Slattery (2nd from left) and Mark Malone (right), homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04925; Hart, Tom
    People; Slattery, Robert; Malone, Mark
  - David Farrell, Ron Squillacioti, unknown person, Peter Demetre, unkown person, Jim and Theresa McNice, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04926; Hart, Tom
    People; Farrell, David; Squillicioti, Richard; Demetre, Peter; McNice, James; McNice, Theresa
  - At Jumbo Lounge in Teele Square, Dan Donovan, Ron Squillacioti, John Perkins, Peter Viris, David Farrell, Mark Malone, and Dennis Weed, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04927; Hart, Tom
    People; Donovan, Dan; Squillicioti, Richard; Perkins, John; Viris, Peter; Farrell, David; Malone, Mark; Weed, Dennis
  - At Jumbo Lounge in Teele Square, Dan Donahue, Peter Viris, John Perkins, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04928; Hart, Tom
    People; Donahue, Dan; Viris, Peter; Perkins, John
  - At Jumbo Lounge in Teele Square, unknown person, Ron Squillicioti, Dan Donahue and Peter Viris, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04929; Hart, Tom
    People; Squillicioti, Richard; Donahue, Dan; Viris, Peter
  - At Jumbo Lounge in Teele Square, Robert Lee, Russell Collin's wife, Russell Collins, and Mark Malone (looking away), homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04930; Hart, Tom
    People; Lee, Robert; Collins, Russ; Malone, Mark
  - Hillside House kitchen, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04931; Hart, Tom
  - John Kiley, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04932; Hart, Tom
    People; Kiley, John
  - Dave and Sandy Farrell, homecoming, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04933; Hart, Tom
    People; Farrell, David; Farrell, Sandy
  - Corner of Dearborn Road and College Avenue, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04935; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House trophy cabinet, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04936; Hart, Tom
    Trophies
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04937; Hart, Tom
    People; Athletics; Basketball; Boston Celtics
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04938; Hart, Tom
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04939; Hart, Tom
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04940; Hart, Tom
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04941; Hart, Tom
  - Boston Celtics practice at Cousens Gym, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04942; Hart, Tom
  - Wren Hall dorm room, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04943; Hart, Tom
  - Wren Hall dorm room, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04944; Hart, Tom
  - Wren Hall dorm room, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04945; Hart, Tom
  - View from Wren Hall dorm room, October, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04946; Hart, Tom
    Dormitories
  - Lawn from Wessell Library towards Robinson Hall, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04947; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library roof, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04948; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04949; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04950; Hart, Tom
  - Looking down Memorial Steps towards College Avenue, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04951; Hart, Tom
    Stairs; Exterior views
  - Goddard Chapel, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04952; Hart, Tom
    Chapels; Exterior views
  - David and Sandy Farrell, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04953; Hart, Tom
  - Doug Boari and friends, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04954; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Boari, Doug
  - Bob Slattery, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04955; Hart, Tom
    Students; People; Slattery, Robert
  - Unknown student, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04956; Hart, Tom
    People; Students
  - Peter Viris and Richard Squillicioti, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04957; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Viris, Peter; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Student in Hillside House kitchen, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04958; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Kitchens
  - Students in Hillside House kitchen, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04959; Hart, Tom
  - Hillside House, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04960; Hart, Tom
  - View of Wessell Library from Professors Row, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04961; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04962; Hart, Tom
  - Goddard Chapel, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04963; Hart, Tom
  - Ballou Hall, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04964; Hart, Tom
  - Wessell Library, 1981; MS093.001.DO.04965; Hart, Tom
  - Rent-a-Jumbo, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04966; Hart, Tom
    People; Elephants
  - Rent-a-Jumbo, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04967; Hart, Tom
  - Football crowd, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04968; Hart, Tom
    People; Crowds; Football
  - Doug Boari at football game, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04969; Hart, Tom
    People; Crowds; Football; Boari, Doug
  - View of end zone, football game, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04970; Hart, Tom
  - Crowd at football game, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04971; Hart, Tom
  - Richard Squillicioti at Hillside House, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04972; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; Squillicioti, Richard
  - Football game, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04973; Hart, Tom
  - Football game, homecoming, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04974; Hart, Tom
  - Jim and Theresa McNice at Hillside House, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04975; Hart, Tom
    People; Students; McNice, James; McNice, Theresa
  - Hillside House kitchen: Mark Malone, Jim McNice, and Peter Wadler, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04976; Hart, Tom
    People; Malone, Mark; McNice, James; Wadler, Peter
  - John Kiley and Bob Slattery, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04977; Hart, Tom
    People; Kiley, John; Slattery, Robert
  - Tufts students, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04978; Hart, Tom
  - John Capone, center, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04979; Hart, Tom
    People; Capone, John
  - Tufts graduates, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04980; Hart, Tom
  - Tufts graduates, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04981; Hart, Tom
  - John Capone, second from left, and Peter Demetre, with hat, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04982; Hart, Tom
    People; Capone, John; Demetre, Peter
  - Mark Malone, right, 1983; MS093.001.DO.04983; Hart, Tom
    People; Malone, Mark
  - Bromfield Pearson Building, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04984; Hart, Tom
  - Ballou Hall, right, and Goddard Chapel, June, 1966; MS093.001.DO.04985; Hart, Tom